totaleisure.com 2015-10-05

# North America totaleisure.com Privacy Policy - Over 250000 hotels worldwide, vacation packages, excursions, and cruises

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.totaleisure.com and 6 Continents Travel Network, LLC DBA totaleisure.com and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to 6 Continents Travel Network, LLC DBA totaleisure.com include www.totaleisure.com and totaleisure.com. The totaleisure.com website is a travel services including but not limited to hotel bookings, vacation/travel packages, transfers, tickets for attractions and excursions, and corporate travel site. By using the totaleisure.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

totaleisure.com may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. totaleisure.com may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, race and location. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by totaleisure.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the totaleisure.com website.

totaleisure.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from totaleisure.com so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. totaleisure.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the totaleisure.com website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

totaleisure.com collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

totaleisure.com may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from totaleisure.com and its affiliates. totaleisure.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

totaleisure.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

totaleisure.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. totaleisure.com may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to totaleisure.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

totaleisure.com may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within totaleisure.com, in order to determine what totaleisure.com services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within totaleisure.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

totaleisure.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on totaleisure.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of totaleisure.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of totaleisure.com, or the public.

**Security of your Personal Information**

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, totaleisure.com uses the following:

Godaddy.com

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Children Under Thirteen**

totaleisure.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from totaleisure.com by contacting us here:

\- Web page: www.totaleisure.com/contactus

\- Email: customerservice@totaleisure.com

\- Phone: +1 888 508 4805

Effective as of August 19, 2013
